final List<Map<String, dynamic>> reactnativeQuiz = [
  {
    'question': 'What is React Native?',
    'options': ['Framework', 'Library', 'Language', 'IDE'],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Who developed React Native?',
    'options': ['Apple', 'Google', 'Facebook', 'Microsoft'],
    'correctAnswer': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which language is used to write React Native apps?',
    'options': ['Java', 'Kotlin', 'JavaScript', 'Swift'],
    'correctAnswer': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following is used for styling in React Native?',
    'options': ['CSS', 'Inline styles', 'Sass', 'CSS-in-JS'],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is a component in React Native?',
    'options': [
      'A function that returns UI',
      'A type of state',
      'A UI element',
      'A helper class'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is used to manage state in React Native?',
    'options': ['setState', 'Redux', 'Context API', 'All of the above'],
    'correctAnswer': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which command is used to initialize a React Native project?',
    'options': [
      'react-native init',
      'react-native start',
      'create-react-app',
      'npm init react-native'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the purpose of the Virtual DOM in React Native?',
    'options': [
      'It provides a faster way to update the UI',
      'It manages user inputs',
      'It handles network requests',
      'It stores the app data'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is Expo in React Native?',
    'options': [
      'A library for managing state',
      'A toolchain for building React Native apps',
      'A router for navigation',
      'A framework for server-side rendering'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is used for navigation in React Native?',
    'options': [
      'react-router',
      'react-navigation',
      'Redux',
      'react-native-navigation'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
];
